const questions: Array<{ question: string; answer: string }> = [
  {
    question: 'What are the different ways a company can hire students from the campus?',
    answer: `The different ways of recruiting students are:<br>
<ul>
  <li>Campus Recruitment Program in which final year students take part.</li>
  <li>Summer Internship Program for pre-final year students, which can be converted into a pre-placement offer.</li>
</ul>`,
  },
  {
    question: 'How can a company register itself for the campus recruitment program?',
    answer:
      'To participate in the campus recruitment program, a company must first contact the Training and Placement Cell and submit a job notification form (JNF). You can also find the detailed placement procedure in the policy linked above.',
  },
  {
    question: 'Is there any fee associated with the process?',
    answer:
      '<b>No.</b> There are no fees associated with the registration or the placement process.',
  },
  {
    question: 'When does the recruitment program start?',
    answer: 'The recruitment season runs throughout the year (from July to May).',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the procedure to schedule a pre-placement talk (PPT)?',
    answer:
      'A company will only be allowed to hold its PPT after filling up the job notification form.  The session is scheduled between 6 PM to 9 PM on weekdays and between 10 AM and 5 PM hours on Saturdays and Sundays. Student volunteers will get in touch with the company to fix a mutually convenient time for the session.',
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of information do the students expect in PPTs?',
    answer: `The pre-placement talk is a platform for interaction between the company and the students. The presentation is followed by a Q&A session where students interact with company officials to better understand the company and potential roles. The crucial insights that the students expect from the PPT are:
<ul>
  <li>Profile and reputation of the corporation</li>
  <li>Career roles and responsibilities offered in different types of profiles</li>
  <li>Locations where the student is likely to be posted</li>
  <li>Compensation packages</li>
</ul>`,
  },
  {
    question: 'On what basis is the slot allotted to a company for the final placement?',
    answer: `Slotting is done subject to the following parameters:
<ul>
  <li>Student preferences</li>
  <li>Work profile</li>
  <li>Compensation package</li>
  <li>Career prospects</li>
  <li>Student intake</li>
  <li>Past relationship with IIIT Kota</li>
</ul>`,
  },
  {
    question: 'Can a company interview the students already placed in another company?',
    answer:
      'IIIT Kota follows a <i>"One Student; One Job"</i> policy. Once a job is registered against a student, they are not entitled to sit for any other company.',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What are the infrastructural facilities available on the campus for the placement process?',
    answer: `The campus is equipped with state of the art communication, computing, and presentation facilities to facilitate a smooth placement process:
<ul>
  <li>Teleconferencing and video conferencing facility</li>
  <li>Linux and Windows lab for online tests</li>
  <li>Centrally air-conditioned auditorium, lecture halls, seminar and conference rooms for presentations, group discussions, and interviews</li>
</ul>`,
  },
  {
    question:
      'Are there multiple companies recruiting in the same slot? How is the case of multiple offers resolved?',
    answer:
      '<b>Yes</b>, there are multiple companies recruiting in the same slot. The results of all the companies are announced at the end of the slot. If a student gets multiple offers, they can choose between them and inform the office of their decision before the next slot.',
  },
];

export default questions;
